{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Which of the following indicates the maximum number of entities that can be involved in a relationship?", "opta": "Minimum cardinality", "optb": "Maximum cardinality", "optc": "ERD", "optd": "Greater Entity Count (GEC)", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which type of entity cannot exist in the database unless another type of entity also exists in the database, but does not require that the identifier of that other entity be included as part of its own identifier?", "opta": "Weak entity", "optb": "Strong entity", "optc": "ID-dependent entity", "optd": "ID- independent entity", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a one-to-many relationship, the entity that is on the one side of the relationship is called a(n) ________ entity.", "opta": "parent", "optb": "child", "optc": "instance", "optd": "subtype", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which type of entity represents an actual occurrence of an associated generalized entity?", "opta": "Supertype entity", "optb": "Subtype entity", "optc": "Archetype entity", "optd": "Instance entity", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A recursive relationship is a relationship between an entity and ________ .", "opta": "itself", "optb": "a subtype entity", "optc": "an archetype entity", "optd": "an instance entity", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following indicates the minimum number of entities that must be involved in a relationship?", "opta": "Minimum cardinality", "optb": "Maximum cardinality", "optc": "ERD", "optd": "Greater Entity Count (GEC)", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following refers to something that can be identified in the users' work environment, something that the users want to track?", "opta": "Entity", "optb": "Attribute", "optc": "Identifier", "optd": "Relationship", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In which of the following is a single-entity instance of one type related to many entity instances of another type?", "opta": "One-to-One Relationship", "optb": "One-to-Many Relationship", "optc": "Many-to-Many Relationship", "optd": "Composite Relationship", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following refers to an entity in which the identifier of one entity includes the identifier of another entity?", "opta": "Weak entity", "optb": "Strong entity", "optc": "ID-dependent entity", "optd": "ID-independent entity", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which type of entity is related to two or more associated entities that each contain specialized attributes that apply to some but not all of the instances of the entity?", "opta": "Supertype entity", "optb": "Subtype entity", "optc": "Archetype entity", "optd": "Instance entity", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An attribute that names or identifies entity instances is a(n):", "opta": "entity.", "optb": "attribute.", "optc": "identifier.", "optd": "relationship.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Properties that describe the characteristics of entities are called:", "opta": "entities.", "optb": "attributes.", "optc": "identifiers.", "optd": "relationships.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In which of the following can many entity instances of one type be related to many entity instances of another type?", "opta": "One-to-One Relationship", "optb": "One-to-Many Relationship", "optc": "Many-to-Many Relationship", "optd": "Composite Relationship", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Entities of a given type are grouped into a(n):", "opta": "database.", "optb": "entity class.", "optc": "attribute.", "optd": "ERD.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is NOT a basic element of all versions of the E-R model?", "opta": "Entities", "optb": "Attributes", "optc": "Relationships", "optd": "Primary keys", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In which of the following is a single-entity instance of one type of related to a single-entity instance of another type?", "opta": "One-to-One Relationship", "optb": "One-to-Many Relationship", "optc": "Many-to-Many Relationship", "optd": "Composite Relationship", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Entities can be associated with one another in which of the following?", "opta": "Entities", "optb": "Attributes", "optc": "Identifiers", "optd": "Relationships", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which type of entity has its relationship to another entity determined by an attribute in that other entity called a discriminator?", "opta": "Supertype entity", "optb": "Subtype entity", "optc": "Archetype entity", "optd": "Instance entity", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which type of entity represents a logical generalization whose actual occurrence is represented by a second, associated entity?", "opta": "Supertype entity", "optb": "Subtype entity", "optc": "Archetype entity", "optd": "Instance entity", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In a one-to-many relationship, the entity that is on the many side of the relationship is called a(n) ________ entity.", "opta": "parent", "optb": "child", "optc": "instance", "optd": "subtype", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}